Andrew Weisbeck

Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina (919) 867-8368 andrew.weisbeck@gmail.com

Web Development

Serving clients by developing web sites and applications by utilizing three years of experience with HTML5, CSS, JS, and Python. Committed to researching, learning, and implementing new languages and software that I have less experience with in order to complete projects.

Exceptional analyst who applies critical thinking skills to assess problems, interpret data, and recommend optimal decisions by evaluating alternative results.

Exemplary communicator boasting a distinguished career building solid partner relationships and influencing people with authentic interactions.

Dynamic teammate with a solid reputation for adapting to new roles quickly, effectively managing projects, and striving for personal and organizational success each day.

Cybersecurity
Threat Analysis
IT Administration
Technical Writing
Market Forecasting
EDR & SIEM
Entrepreneur
Customer Service
Communication
Team Building

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

IRON RANGE CYBER

Raleigh, North Carolina July 2021 - November 2021

Served as a SOC Analyst on a cybersecurity team and was responsible for monitoring and fighting threats on our client's IT infrastructure, assessing security systems and measuring for vulnerabilities and improvements, and contributed in creating standard operating procedures for a cybersecurity startup.

SOC Analyst

- Monitored endpoints, performed security event triage, and responded to incidents while coordinating with team members and management to document and report incidents.
- Identified and remediated security issues with Malwarebytes, Witfoo, and IRIS and followed up by documenting incidents and reporting them to our clients.
- Scanned machines with Nessus and accessed our GUI to gain visibility into our client's networks in order to locate threat vulnerabilities and monitor activity.
- Administered client machines and maintained system software with Atera by creating and deploying scripts in Powershell, remotely connecting to client sessions, and any other system tools.
- Assisted clients by implementing best security practices to make recommendations, create monthly reports, and respond to any needs by effectively communicating via phone or email.
- Created and modified SOP procedures for a cybersecurity startup with team members.

* *

SUNTRUST & TRUIST BANK

Rolesville, North Carolina April 2019 - July 2020

Representative of a large regional bank, responsible for promoting financial wellbeing by consulting individuals and small businesses, developing relationships with clients, facilitating new accounts and loans, and resolving technical issues.

Personal Banker IV

- Expanded assets by over \$1.25 million in new account deposits and loans.
- Improve client relationships by building rapport, providing technical support, and recommending products and services based on their needs.
- Manage the entire loan process from conception to completion.
- Resolve escalated client issues as sole banker with no branch manager, achieving over 95% client experience satisfaction.
- Market products and services to new and existing clients in Central North Carolina to increase branch assets by over 8%.

Andrew WeisbeckPg. 2

 Coordinate budgeting, loan financing, and savings plans to enhance the financial wellbeing of individuals and small businesses.

*** ***

BIRDDOG DISTRIBUTING INC.

Bozeman, Montana Aug 2017 – Feb 2019

Inventory manager, responsible for researching sales trends, facilitating purchase orders, delegating product specifications to manufacturers, and creating quality SEO content.

Purchasing Manager

- Controlled inventory ordering process by analyzing sales data, forecasting consumer demand, validating sufficient capital needs, and organizing inventory transportation logistics.
- Generated over 25% more organic website traffic by composing engaging SEO content.
- Evaluated new products from manufacturers and introduced them through multiple e-commerce channels and print marketing campaigns.
- Negotiated with manufacturers to improve product quality while maintaining cost effectiveness.
- Initiated competitive pricing analysis as part of a marketing strategy to expand market share and boost revenue by 20%.

+ +

EDUCATION

B.S., Business Administration, Minor in Finance, University of Nebraska-Lincoln, 2014.

Organizations

Pi Kappa Alpha Fraternity, IFC Delegate, Merchandise Chair, and Rush Captain, 2010-2014.

Business Professionals of America, Vice President, National Qualifier in Tax Accounting, 2006-2009.

Personal Projects

Rad CyberTech, Design Websites and Apps, provide IT and Business services, and hunt threats in bug bounty programs as a side business (September 2021-Present).

Udemy Learning, Obtained certificates in the following courses: The Complete Cybersecurity Course Volumes I-IV, CCSO - Certified Cloud Security Officer, TOTAL: CompTIA Security+ Certification (SYO-601), and Cybersecurity Operations and Technology Solutions.

Raspberry Pi 4 Cybersecurity System, Constructed a cybersecurity tool with a Raspberry Pi 4 and Ubuntu Linux for Bug Bounty Hunting, learning Penetration Testing, and other programming projects.

Blockchain Application and Network, Creating my own cryptocurrency (Geaux-Coin) through a guided course, using NodeJS and Express (About 50% completed).

CompTIA Security +, Currently studying so I can earn my certification - planning on taking the exam in January 2021.

Developing Web Portfolio, In the process of creating web portfolio to display projects and achievements https://geauxweisbeck4.github.io/cv/